hello.
こんにちわ
こん にちわ
It's cute.
かわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you doing something with each of us?
何か僕ずつとかやってるんすか?
I played badminton when I was in junior high school.
中学の時にバダミントンやってました
Even now?
今も?
Especially?
別に?
Did you do it?
やった?
going home club?
帰宅部?
Do you have any kind of part-time job?
なんかバイトとかしてるの?
I work part-time at a bar.
バイト、居酒屋やってます
Can high school students open an izakaya?
高校生って居酒屋できるのか?
Especially?
別に?
But it's something I'm doing individually.
でも個人でやってるところだから
It's pretty loose, that's why.
結構緩いんだよ、だから
Well, if you're cute, don't you get teased at pubs?
なんか さ、かわいいとさ、居酒屋とかだといじられたりしない?
There may be a lot of strange old men out there.
変なおじさんは多いかもしれないですね
What do they say?
なんて言われる?
It's like Darugarami.
だるがらみみたいな
It's cute.
かわいいね
It seems like customers are exchanging contact seats.
お客さんから連絡席交換されるみたいな
There are times when I am asked.
聞かれた時はある
Will it not be given?
渡されないとか?
That's not true.
それはないですね
Are you going to name the person who taught you?
教えた人にするんですか?
OF.
NG
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏居る?
I'm not there.
居ないです
How much?
どれくらい?
About a year.
1年くらい
Don't you need it now?
いらないんですか、今?
I don't need it.
いらない
I don't think it's fun to be alone.
別に一人で楽しいみたいな
There's no such thing as a day off, right?
休みとかないでしょ?
I sleep during my days off.
休みは寝てます
Why don't you go play?
遊びに行かないの?
now.
今
But even though I go out with friends, I just sleep even when I don't really have anything to do.
でも友達と遊びには行くけど、 本当に用事がない時もひたすら寝
I will.
て ます
Would you like to go on a date?
デートとかしないですか?
Do you want time alone?
一人の時間欲しいかな?
We didn't really go out and have fun together,
あんまりみんなでワイワイとか遊びに行ったりとか、
Don't you like that?
そういうの好きじゃない?
I like it.
好きですよ
It seems like sleep is important.
睡眠大事みたいな
Why are you staying up late?
なんで、夜更かししてるの?
I'm really into it.
めっちゃしてます
what are you doing?
何してるの?
I'm watching YouTube.
YouTube見てます
Do you have any YouTubers you recommend?
おすすめのYouTuberはいりますか?
Tokai On Air.
東海オンエアとか
What is interesting about it?
どういうところが面白いですか?
all.
全部
for example?
例えば?
for example...
例えば...
I just don't understand.
ちょっとわかんない
Interesting for now.
とりあえず面白い
Planning ability.
企画力とか
企画力
It's kind of interesting, I guess.
ちょっと面白いかな、みたいな
Are you looking elsewhere?
他を見るんですか?
Various YouTube?
いろんなYouTube?
It's like Johnny's.
ジャニーズとかですからね
Do you have Johnny's?
ジャニーズあるんですか?
There is.
ありますよ
It's like an official channel.
公式チャンネルみたいな
Who do you like?
誰が好きなんですか?
It's a secret.
秘密です
I won't say it.
言いません
Is there anyway?
もしが一応いるんですか?
I'm here.
います
Secretly?
内緒で?
Do you have many secrets?
秘密が多いですか?
secret.
秘密
There are many secrets.
秘密多い
I have a lot of secrets...
いっぱい秘密があるんですけど...
Can I take a video?
映像で撮ってはいいですか?
It's a secret.
秘密ですよ
Is it okay to be biased?
偏っていたところはいいですか?
I'll think about it.
考えておきます
They're all there.
そろってしてますね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
How tall are you?
身長はどれくらいですか?
It is 166.
166です
Can I look behind you?
後ろも見ていいですか?
Where do you go out?
どこ出かけたりするんですか?
where?
どこ?
Are you going to Hasabi?
ハサビに行ったりするの?
My current child.
今の子は
Lots of shopping in various places.
いろんなとこ買い物いっぱい
You have a beautiful butt.
綺麗なお尻してますね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is it you?
自分ですか?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
じゃなきれいですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's pretty big.
結構大きいよね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Have you ever been seen while walking?
歩いてて見られたしない?
Do you notice nature?
自然って気付く?
What about nature?
自然は?
I'm being watched.
見られてるな
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
Is that so?
そういうの?
I guess that's not the case.
そんなないかな
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
That's definitely the case.
どんにもそういうね
It's really big.
めっちゃ大きいですね
No, not at all.
いや、全然
That's fine.
いいです
How big does it take?
どれくらいで大きくなるんですか?
How long?
どれくらいで?
Yeah.
うん
I wonder how many, about 5 or so.
5つくらいくつぐらいかな
5...
About 2nd grade.
2年生ぐらい
Maybe 2 or 3 years.
2、3年とかかな
It's recent.
最近なんだぞ
Are you coming suddenly?
急に来るの?
I don't know.
わかんない
What if you notice?
気づいたら?
Like.
みたいな
There doesn't seem to be any cider.
サイダーはないみたいな
not at all.
全然
I don't really understand?
あんまわかんない?
Yeah.
うん
It's beautiful.
綺麗だよ
yes.
そう
That's amazing.
すごいね
Try lifting it up with both hands.
ちょっと両手で持ち上げてみて
Clean up a lot.
めっちゃ片付ける
happy.
嬉しい
This is quite heavy.
結構これ重たいね
Do you want to be hard?
固い固いする?
not at all.
全然
I don't really understand?
あんまわかんない?
It feels very heavy.
すごい重量感が
feel?
感じる?
Yeah.
うん
secret.
秘密
Yeah?
うん?
Not much?
あんまり?
Look at the back carefully.
後ろよくかかってごらん
absolutely.
全く
Don't you ever get horny?
ムラムラしたりしないの?
do not.
しない
Lie.
嘘つけ
I don't do it myself.
自分ではしないです
There isn't.
ないんだよ
Do you usually feel something?
普段どこか感じる?
How does it feel good to be treated?
どうされると気持ちいい?
Will you touch me?
触られるの?
Yeah.
うん
Pretty smooth?
結 構ツルツル?
Are you making it smooth?
ツルツルにしてるの?
I'm doing it.
にはしてる
Smoothly.
ツルツルに
I do it extensively myself.
自分で広くやってる
When did you start shaving?
いつから剃ったんですか?
About 5,512.
5、512くらい
Why do you shave?
なんで剃っちゃうの?
Because I had a boyfriend?
彼氏いたから?
Will you shave your head if you get a boyfriend?
彼氏できると剃っちゃうのか?
why?
なんで?
Don't you hate it if you shave a lot?
いっぱい剃ったらちょっと嫌かな?
That's it.
って
I'm happier when it's smooth.
ツ ルツルのほうがうれしい
What is smooth?
ツルツルは何?
Do you want me to lick you?
舐めてほしい?
Well, that's part of it, but there's a bit of a stick growing out of it.
まあそれもあるけど、ちょっと棒は生えてる
Hey, woman?
ねえ、女?
That doesn't seem to be the case.
ってちょっとねえみたいな
Do you care?
気にするの?
Socially.
社会的に
Feels good.
気持ちいい